let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"How many members are in SEVENTEEN?",
        answer:"13",
        options:[
            "13",
            "17",
            "10"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"What is member Seungkwan's family name?",
        answer:"Boo",
        options:[
            "Boo",
            "Lee",
            "Choi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Which company is SEVENTEEN under?",
        answer:"Pledis Entertainment",
        options:[
            "Pledis Entertainment",
            "SM Entertainment",
            "Starship Entertainment"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"Who is the main producer of SEVENTEEN?",
        answer:"Woozi",
        options:[
            "S.Coups",
            "Dino",
            "Woozi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Where was member Vernon born?",
        answer:"New York",
        options:[
            "California",
            "New York",
            "Virginia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"Which of the following choices is NOT a Hip Hop Unit song?",
        answer:"Swimming Fool",
        options:[
            "Check-In",
            "If I",
            "Swimming Fool"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Which track was nominated for the 2021 MTV Video Music Awards?",
        answer:"Ready to Love",
        options:[
            "Ready to Love",
            "Not Alone (Hitorijanai)",
            "Rock With You"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"SEVENTEEN has a YouTube series called",
        answer:"Going SEVENTEEN",
        options:[
            "RUN SEVENTEEN",
            "Going SEVENTEEN",
            "SEVENTEEN Live"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"How tall is member Mingyu?",
        answer:"6'2”",
        options:[
            "5’10”",
            "6’0”",
            "6'2”"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"Member Hoshi's solo debut is titled",
        answer:"Spider",
        options:[
            "Eye of the Tiger",
            "Spider",
            "Tarantula"
        ]
    }

];